字幕製作：~Me愛FFS/WTF
時間軸校對：~Me愛FFS/WTF
轉載請保留作者名字
2005年科學家們發現了一顆
In 2005,Scientists discovered a distant planet
氣候條件與地球極為相似的遙遠行星
which has a climate almost identical to that of earth
2006年美國國家航空航天局製造了一個
In 2006,NASA constructed a transmission device
比以前功能強大五倍的傳送裝置
that was many times more powerful than those already in existence
並開始了接觸該行星的計劃
They developed a program to get in contact with this distant planet
這就是"燈塔"項目
The program was known as "Project Beacon"
喜馬拉雅山脈 "燈塔" 國際項目
今天標誌著一次史無前例的
Today really marks the first stage of an
科技進步開始進入第一階段
unprecedented technological advancement
我們已經發現了一顆
We have begun to identify a so-called
所謂的宜居行星
goldilocks planet
這些行星與它們的太陽的關係
these planets that share a similar relationship
和地球很相似
with their sun as we have with ours
如果行星離它的太陽太遠
If a planet's too far away from it's sun
就會很冷
it's too cold
離得太近又太熱
If it's too close to it's sun.it's too hot
而類地行星與其太陽的距離剛剛好
But for an earthlike planet,the distance is just right
最適宜生命生存和繁衍
Potentially perfect for sustaining life
現在我們終於找到了這樣一顆行星
We have finally managed to identify one planet
它與它的太陽距離正好 存在液態水
that is the right distance from it's star to hold water
它的質量不多不少 使它擁有大氣層
And is the right mass to sustain an atmosphere.
每隔二十四小時 我們在夏威夷的數據站
Every 24 hours our station in hawaii will
就會向深太空衛星
transmit a signal
陸地衛星七號發射一次信號
to LANSAT 7,our deep orbiting satellite
衛星會把信號放大 傳送給目標行星
which will amplify & relay the signal to our targeted
我們把這顆行星命名為G行星
planet which is rather grandly entitled .Planet G
如果宇宙裡有智能生命來到地球
if there is intelligent life out there,and they come here
就會像哥倫布碰到印第安人一樣
it's gonna be like Columbus & the Indians.
我們是印第安人
Only we're the indians
女士們先生們
Ladies and gentlemen
請準備好親眼目睹這歷史性的一刻
please prepare to bare witness to the making of history
傳送開始
Start transmission
夏威夷  歐湖島
生日快樂 弟弟
Happy birthday little brother
我祝你事業成功 更成熟
Whishing you successs & growth
快樂幸福 祝你今年交好運
A great year
謝謝 我會交好運的
It's gonna be a great year
-我愛你  -我也愛你
-I love you  -I love you too
根據我們霍伯家一貫的傳統
So in the great Hopper family tradition
今年我要引用約翰·伍登的話
this year i'm quoting from coach John Wooden
約翰啊?
John?
逆境能讓我們不再為受人崇拜所累
Adversity is the state in which man
讓我們能夠更容易認識自己
most easily becomes aquainted with himself
乾杯!
Cheers!
-這話太掃興了 -這話很適合你
I'm not cheersing to that.-It's a very good quote for you
我現在是很平凡 可我還年輕呢
I may be free of admirers right now but there's still time
閉嘴 點上蠟燭舉起酒杯
Would you shut up .Light your cupcake & raise your glass
是你買的嗎?
Did you get me that?
對 我買的
Yes I got you that
-謝謝 你真好 -沒什麼!
Thank you.That's very sweet-You're welcome!
我有個朋友托尼
I got this guy,Tony
他說能幫你在工地找份活兒
He said he could get you a construction job
只要你給他打電話
All you need to do is call him
我要杯啤酒和一份雞肉卷
Can I get a beer and a chicken Burrito,please
對不起
Sorry
廚房已經關了
The kitchen's closed
代我向托尼問好
Give Tony my best
不過我不需要你們幫我找工作
But I don't need you or Tony's help for that matter.
去找他或者像我一樣參軍
well you can call him or join me in the navy
不
No
好吧 隨便你
alright! alright
把蠟燭吹滅了然後許個願吧
Blow out the candle and make a wish.
別把它浪費在姑娘身上
Do not waste a wish on a girl
許願要份工作 要套房子
Wish for a job,an apartment
或者新的汽車發電機
a new alternating belt
省得我老給你當司機 要工作吧
so i don't have to drive you everywhere,a job or a
你說了兩次工作
You said you job twice
我過生日
It's my birthday
我自己許願 行嗎?
My wish.Alright?
別浪費了
Please don't waste it
你還是浪費了 對嗎?
You just wasted a wish
-我去了 -勸你別去
-I'm going in -You're not going in.
我怎麼樣?
How do i look?
等等 我看看
Wait let me just fix
帥呆了
Awesome
公主 王子來了
Alright princess go get em
出師不利啊
Great start!
想來點兒什麼?
What seems to be the problem?
我想要份雞肉卷
I want a chicken burrito
強尼 給她做一份
Johnny,chicken burrito her
-別做夢了 - 給她做一份
-It ain't happening - Chicken burrito her
廚房關了 霍伯
The kitchen's closed Hopper
你叫什麼名字?
What's your name?
我很餓
I'm hungry
這不是你的名字
That's not your name
如果你給我五分鐘
If you give me 5 minutes
我會幫你弄一份雞肉卷
I will get you your chicken burrito
五分鐘 現在開始
Five  minutes,starting now
我去弄份雞肉卷
Chicken burrito time.I'm out
雞肉卷 明白
Chicken burrito,roger that
等等 別關門
Wait! Wait! Hi!
麻煩你再開開門
Let's just one twist of the key & we'll be good
嗨 夫人 你好嗎?
how are you madame.How you doing?
雞肉卷就在那兒
The burritos are right there
關門了 你來得太晚了
We're closed Too late bro
行了 就在那兒 求你了
It' right there! Please!
這麼晚別吃雞肉卷 熱量很高的
It's late to eat a burrito.Too many complex carbs
三塊九毛九 就在那兒
$3.99.are right there
雞肉卷
Chicken Burrito
上去 上去
up up!
我弄到了! 站住
I got it!  Don't move
我弄到了! 不許動!
I got it! Don't move!
我弄到雞肉卷了!
I got the Burrito!
我弄到了 不許動
I got it! Don't move!
站住 趴在地上
Don't move! Stay down!
趴在地上 別動
Stay down!
我受夠了!
I've had it!
看看你自己
Look at yourself!
非得把一切搞得一團糟嗎?
How is it that you screw everything up!
對了 昨天晚上那個姑娘
by the way,that girl you were trying to impress last night
知道她爸是誰嗎?
do you know who her father is?
是謝恩上將! 整個艦隊都歸他管
Admiral Shane! He runs the whole damn fleet
這下我的飯碗也砸了 把我的生活也毀了
So now you're messing with job.My life!
你認識她
You know that girl?
雞肉卷美女
The burrito girl?
我從來沒強迫你做過什麼事
Oh I've always stayed out of your business haven't I?
我總是希望哪一天
Coz i was hoping that maybe one day
你能吸取教訓 能懂事點 成熟點
you would learn from your mistakes grow up,mature a bit
我背上有傷嗎?
Is my back alright?
我的天哪 好疼啊
Argh oh my god my back!
你都二十六了 做成什麼事了
You're 26 and what have you got?
你就攢了六十五美元
65 dollars to your name!
我被電了
I got tazed!
一輛開不動的車 還住我的房子
A car that doesn't start,you're living on my couch!
那玩意兒真厲害
Those things work?
看看你自己
Man look at yourself
天哪
Oh My God
從現在開始
As of now
我不能再讓你放任自流了
as of right this second there's a new dynamic at play
從現在起除非有特殊情況
this dynamic is the final from here on out until I state otherwise
我不會再跟你討價還價 不會再跟你商量 更不會讓步
there'll be no more debate,no more discussion,no more compromise
現在我說了算
It's me speaking you listening
叫你做什麼 你就做什麼
me saying you doing
聽明白了嗎?
Do you understand that?
我要讓你洗心革面 重新開始
It's time for a new course of action.A new direction
做點正經事
A game change
我要你加入海軍
You're joining me in the navy
超級戰艦
直播! 直擊! 請看夏威夷新聞
Live! Local! This is Hawaii news now
大量的軍艦開赴夏威夷
Thousands of sailors on dozens of ships are coming to hawaii
參加環太平洋聯合軍演
for RIMPAC
環太平洋聯合軍演
RIMPAC
是規模最大的跨國海上演習
is the world's largest multinational maritime exercise
就像由十四國海軍表演的軍事芭蕾
RIMPAC is  a militarty ballet of 14 navies
有兩萬多人蔘加演習
20,000 navy personnel
目的是加強國家間的合作和協同性
Coorporation & callibration amongst the countries
促進國家間的關係
is the goal.Relationship building is the key
並非所有的活動都在海上進行
Not all the action is taking place out on the water
陸地上也會舉行一些體育活動
there will also be sporting events here on land
忘了世界盃吧
Forget world cup
來看環太平洋聯合杯決賽!
this is the RIMPAC cup final!
和往常一樣夏威夷又是個好天
It's another beautiful day here in Hawaii as ususal!
說得沒錯 不過賽場上陰雲密布
brewing on the field as the scrapy
美國隊和日本隊發生了多次衝突
USA team butting heads with Japan
目前比分是二比零
Score is two nil Japan
美國隊打得很被動
The US has been trailing all day
隊長亞歷克斯·霍伯得激勵一下隊員
aptain Alex Hopper has got to do something to rally the troops here
加油啊
Turn it up!
救得好 漂亮
Big save
斯通·霍伯今天的表現非常出色
by Stone Hoppe rHe is in excellent condition today!
怎麼了 裝什麼?
What's wrong with you drama queen!
快起來 小妞
Get up princess! Come on!
美國隊的奧蒂橫向傳球給了艾倫
USA's 40 squares the ball over to No.6,Alan
克萊夫腳後跟傳球給了霍伯 射門
Clive with a little back-heal pass Hopper! Goooaaal!!
霍伯的表現太驚人了
Hopper you're Hero
美國隊總算得分了
The US is finally on the board
他們終於振作起來了
showing some signs of life
現在比分是二比一
putting the score 2 to 1 Japan
進入傷停補時階段
now Into stoppage time
美國隊能追平比分嗎?
Can the US tie with Japan?
還有多少時間?
Time,Time! Time!
還有一分鐘
A minute left!
亞歷克斯 準備接球
Hey Alex! It's coming your way
斯通·霍伯開出一個好球
Stone Hopper's placed it perfectly!
球彈得比較高
The ball played is too high
亞歷克斯·霍伯準備接球 沒有越位
Hopper's underneath it and onside
嘿 裁判!
Hey ref!
裁判做出判罰 美國隊得到一個點球
A penalty kick has been awarded to the United States
永田和霍伯在禁區相遇
Nagate mad contact with Hopper inside the box
永田踢到了霍伯的臉
By contact you mean Nagate kicked him in the face
-怎麼樣? - 我沒事
-You alright? - Yeah,I'm fine
我沒事 不用你幫忙
I'm fine.I don't need your help
我讓布朗森替你! 布朗森!
Bronson's gonna take it.Bronson!
你什麼意思?布朗森?用不著 我很好!
What do you mean,Bronson? Negative! I'm fine!
布朗森 你來替霍伯
Bronson,you're gonna take this!
布朗森 別過來
Bronson,don't move!
過來 布朗森
Bronson,come here!
布朗森 再往前邁一步你就完了
Bronson,you move one more step you're dead
你今天想死嗎? 想找死嗎?
Do you wanna die today? Do you wanna die?
很明智
Good choice.
他的腦子被踢壞了
He's defintely concussed
我沒事 你威脅我的水手?
Did you just threaten one of my CO's?
由弟弟亞歷克斯·霍伯來罰球
Looks like it's going to be his little brother Alex Hopper
如果我是斯通 就換個前鋒罰球
If I were Stone I would've picked another shooter.
我估計霍伯剛才傷得可不輕啊
I'm skceptical whether Hopper...
集中精神 我能行的!
Concentrate! Focus!
世上有兩種笨蛋 霍伯
There are two kinds of idiots Hopper
一種看著他踢的地方
One who looks away he kicks
另一種沒看著他踢的地方
other looks away he doesn't kick
你是哪一種?
Which idiot are you?
我要用球踢爛你們守門員的臉
I'm the idiot who's gonna kick it through your keepers face
準備打加時賽吧
Get ready for overtime
大家都看著霍伯
All eyes on Hopper
美國隊能扳平比分嗎?
He could send this into overtime
他要射門了 如果霍伯得分..
And here we go! If Hopper...
美國隊就能進入加時賽
US goes into overtime
霍伯這球離球門十萬八千里 沒有任何進球可能
Hopper sends it flying over the crossba Nowhere near the goal
糟糕
Typical
美國隊失去了最後的機會
What a heartbreak for the US
這對已經受傷亞歷克斯·霍伯來說是很糟糕的嘗試
It was a very poor attempt by the obviously injured Alex Hopper
他堅持要求繼續參加比賽
He refused to come out of the game
導致了美國隊在決賽中失利
and his stubborness cost the US
祝賀日本隊
Congratulations to Japan
獲得了2012年環太平洋聯合杯賽的冠軍
Our 2012 RIMPAC Cup winners
比賽結果日本隊以二比一戰勝了美國隊
The Final as we sign off:Japan 2,USA 1
- 你準備好了嗎? - 當然
- Are you ready for this? - Born
你確定嗎?
You sure?
我從來沒這麼確定過
Never been more sure of anything in my life
你要怎麼說?
What are you gonna say?
我會走到他面前
I'm gonna walk up to him man to man,
直視他的眼睛
look him straight in the eyes
- 你會怎麼說 - 我都想好了
- With what words? - My words
好吧
Ok.
長官
Sir.
您的女兒是我見過的最好的姑娘
You're daughter is the best thing that has ever happened to me
她聰明 善良 美麗 風趣
She's smart,kind,beautiful,funny
我深深地愛著她
I'm madly in love with her
希望您能允許我娶她為妻
It would be an honor to have your permission to marry her
我愛你
I love you
我也愛你
I love you too
美國海軍戰艦  密蘇裡號戰列艦  強大的MO
首先歡迎各位參加環太平洋聯合軍事演習
First off I would like to welcome you all to the RIMPAC international naval war games
歡迎各位登臨美國海軍史上
I'ld like to welcome you on-board
最偉大的戰艦
the greatest fighting ship in american naval history
強大的MO 密蘇裡號戰列艦
the MIGHTY MO.The USS MISSOURI
見鬼!
Shit!
霍伯 你的帽子
Hopper, your cover!
你繼續走你的
Keeping you on your toes
霍伯 快走! 快點!霍伯
Hopper! Let's go,come on! Hopper
這邊? 不 不 不
This way? No no no
這邊是上將 我知道
That way's the Admiral.I knew that
密蘇裡號是美國建造的最後一艘戰列艦
The USS Missouri was the final battleship to be completed by the United States
現在這種大型戰列艦已被現代化的 小型軍艦所取代
before being decomisioned and replaced by a more modern fleet of vessels,
比如驅逐艦
like Destroyers
戰列艦和驅逐艦有什麼區別呢?
What's the diference between a battleship and a destroyer?
戰列艦是很大的船
Battleships are great ships,
有點像恐龍 是用來抵擋攻擊的
they're kinda like dinosaurs They're designed to take hits
有點像練拳擊用的沙袋
Kinda like a floating punching bag.
驅逐艦比較小 可是非常酷
But then there are destroyers which are just awesome
它們像終結者一樣摧毀敵人
They're designed to dish it out like the Terminator!
你是艦長嗎?
Are you a captain?
不 他不是艦長
No he's not a captain
因為他老是遲到 快走!
because he's always late.Come on!
我為船而戰
I fight the ship
快走! 會更好的!
Come on! Which is even better
聽著 搞定它
Listen get it done.Get it done
寶貝放心吧 我能搞定的
Babe it's a formality.I'm all over it
好的! 去吧!
Ok! Go!
今天在座的有
We have with us today,
曾在密蘇裡號上服役的老兵
veterans from the MISSOURI
有些人還參加過二戰
Who have served on her,some going back to WWII
他們是最優秀士兵的榜樣
Examples of the finest men to have ever served in any navy
霍伯上尉 真榮幸您能大駕光臨
Lt.Hopper,what an honor thank you for joining us
很高興來這裡
Good to be here
接下來將開始本年度的軍事演習
And now as we prepare to embark in this outstanding
- 我好緊張 - 把眼鏡摘了
- I'm nervous - Shades off
有請各位艦長到台上來
I would like the commanding officers to come to the stage
來自日本的永田上校
Captain Nagata,Japan
你好!
Konnichiwa!
馬來西亞的盧上校
Captain Lou,Malaysia.
哈嘍!哈嘍!
Allo! Allo!
跟我們的說法差不多
It's so close.Like the way we say it
- 他討厭我 - 沒有
- He hates me - He doesn't hate you!
閉嘴 別說話
Shut up,shut up
澳大利亞的傑克上校
Captain Jacks,Australia!
- 你好!  - 閉嘴!
- G'Day! - Shut up!
- 新加坡的曹上校 - 你好
- Captain Zhao,Singapore! - G'Day.
- 給我閉嘴 - 你好
- Shut up! - G'Day
最後有請美國海軍的斯通·霍伯中校
A special acknowledgment to Commander Stone Hopper,US Navy
保持冷靜  別煩我
Stay calm.Knock em out
他和他的戰友們在去年的演習中
who along with his outstanding crew and ship
拿到了總分第一
had the highest overall rating last year
把眼鏡摘了 霍伯!
Shades off Hopper!
- 中校 - 謝謝 上將
- Commander.- Thank you Admiral
歡迎各位 很高興今天在這裡見到大家
Welcome everybody it's really great to see you all here today
各位老前輩 向你們致敬
Especially you gentlemen.It's a true honor
今年我和我的戰友們壓力很大
Me and my crew are gonna have to be on our toes this year
你們的軍艦都很先進
Because your ships look outstanding
戰士訓練有素
and your men look ready
祝大家好運
So good luck out there!
注意安全 積極作戰
Be safe! Keep chargin!
爸爸愛女兒
He loves his daughter
女兒愛你 他會同意的
She loves you.he's gonna respect that
嘿 邁克!
Hey,Mike!
上將
Admiral!
你還記得薩姆嗎?
You remember Sam?
都這年頭了 還要問父母意見
It's an obsolete tradition.Just asking for permission
-這到底是誰想出來的? - 行了
-Tell me that came from? - Stop
薩姆是理療師
Sam is a physical therapist
別胡思亂想了
Stop worrying about this.
趕快過去辦正事吧
and walk up and do what you gotta do
你好 霍伯!
Hello Hopper!
你來這幹嗎?
Why are you here?
這下可有的瞧了
This is gonna be sweet!
我當時是合理爭搶
I was within the rules.
踢人家臉也算合理爭搶?
Were you within the rules when you kicked me in the face?
你不是有重要的事要辦嗎?
Isn't there some place more important you need to be right now.
霍伯恨死他了
He hates the man!
這好像有點幼稚 不是嗎?
Well that seems a bit juvenile,wouldn't you say?
你去惹他看看
You go mess with him and see what happens!
為什麼? 去啊
Why? do
他這笑算什麼意思?
Would it be funny if i punched you in the face? Would that be funny?
膽小鬼 回家吃肯德基吧
Chicken! Kentucky Fried Chicken!
我喜歡 味道很好
Yeap.I love it.Two piece
你長得也像肯德基爺爺
You look like Colonel Sanders actually.
他是個帥哥
He was a handsom man.
爸爸你剛才說得真好
Good job out there Dad!
你要幹嗎?
What do you want?
霍伯想占用你五分鐘時間
Hopper needs 5 minutes of your time.
夠了 幹嗎? 我只是想
That's enough! What do you mean that's enough?
你不是有更重要的事要辦嗎?
Isn't there something more important you should be doing right now?
最多三分鐘
Three minutes,tops.
謝謝 我愛你 謝謝爸爸
Thank you,I love you.Thank you daddy
我也愛你
I love you too.
- 他會揍我的 - 他不會揍你的
- He's gonna smash my face in - He's not gonna smash your face in..
天哪
Oh my god.
長官 我真的很榮幸
Sir it would be an honour
長官
Sir! sir! sir!
能有幸得到您的許可
Give me your permission..It would be an honor to have your permission
長官 你到底同不同意
Sir,give me your permission what's your deal?
如果能得到您的許可
It would be a thankful honor to have your permission
能和您牽手 什麼?
to honor your hand..What?
天哪
Oh my god
長官 我能娶您的女兒嗎?
Sir,May i please marry your daughter?
她是我的一切 我愛她
She's everything i have and i love her
在這兒自言自語呢?霍伯?
Talking to yourself Mr.Hopper?
是啊
Yea I was.
我在說你的壞話呢 永田
I was actually talking about you Nagata
你這個白痴 你瘋了嗎?
You idiot you crazy?
長官 這是一次意外事故
Sir,it was a fluke accident
洗手間的地板很滑
The bathroom floor was wet
我摔倒了
I began to fall
永田上校正好進來想扶我
Cpt.Nagata kindly reached out to help
我們撞到一起
Our heads go bang!
我們退後 又撞到了
We fall back.Bang again
就像是傑瑞·路易斯
Just like the great Jerry Lewis
傑瑞·路易斯?
Jerry Lewis?
喜劇演員傑瑞·路易斯嗎?
Did he just say Jerry Lewis?
是的 長官
Yes,sir
你在開玩笑嗎?
Are you kidding me?
他演的《服務生》
還有《肥佬教授》
and
都是經典電影
Very good movies.
他是一個偉大的慈善家 長官
He's a great humanitarian,sir
你們根本沒意識到問題的嚴重性
You both think this a joke then you're very  much mistaken
不許再發生這種事
This will not happen again.
聽明白了嗎?
Do i make myself clear?
是 長官
Yes,sir!
先生們 我要和霍伯單獨談談
Gentlemen.Give me a minute with Mr Hopper.
你到底在想什麼?
What is wrong with you?
你很有才能 可我沒見過
You've got skills,but i have never ever
像你這麼不思進取的
seen a man waste them like you.
讓船隻遠離怒濤和激浪
Keep the ship out of the surf and spray
否則你將粉身碎骨
or we will plunge to desturction
《荷馬史詩》長官
,sir
就是這一點最讓我受不了
The fact that you know that infuriates me beyond words
我真想不通我女兒看上你哪兒了
What my daughter sees in you is a great mystery to me
你的確很有才華
You're a very smart individual
可是意志力 領導力 決策力
with very weak character,leadership
全都差到極點
and decision making skills
你有什麼要對我說的嗎? 有嗎?
Do you have anything to say to me? Anything?
沒有 長官
Negative,sir.
好好享受這次演習吧 霍伯
Enjoy these naval exercises Hopper
可能是你最後一次了 解散
They're likely to be your last.Dismissed.
- 要我幫忙嗎? - 不用
Is there anything i can do to help?- Negative.
- 如果想找人聊聊?  - 我不想
- If you wana talk about anything.- I dont.
如果你改變主意了?
If you change you mind
- 想找人聊聊?  - 不可能
- and you do wanna talk about.- I wont.
那好吧
Roger that.
環太平洋聯合軍事演習
夏威夷 檀香山  第一天
除了上帝 我們攻擊任何人
美國海軍航空母艦 羅納德·裡根號
給我聯繫第一驅逐艦中隊
Contact Efron 1
開始反潛作戰演習
Commence anti-submarine warfare exercises
展開空中行動
Commence all operations
出發了 快走
go go go
戰鬥警報 全體注意
action warning .All stations
美國海軍驅逐艦 桑普森號
下午好 桑普森號
Good afternoon,Samson!
今天是聯合海軍演習的第一天
Welcome to Day One of the RIMPAC Naval War Games
我們來訓練一下團隊作戰技能
We are here to sharpen our skills as a team
美國海軍驅逐艦 約翰·保羅·瓊斯號
作為武器指揮官
As your weapons officer
我要提醒各位
Let me remind you that
這是艘攻擊型的作戰艦艇
this is a combat vessel
我們必須精通所有指揮控制
and we will excel in our commanding control
我想請各位時刻保持警覺
I want everyone to stay frosty
我們面對來自十三個國家的艦隊
We're gonna be close maneuvering with 13 nations out here
我們的任務就是要擊敗所有對手
We are here to crush every other ship
通過實戰學習
I'm excited to see what we learn
來這兒可不是為了學習
We not here in this weapons  room to learn
注意安全 互相照應
Be safe out there and look out for each other
積極作戰
and keep charging
如果這次演習我們表現平平
If we return to Pearl without having outperform
兩手空空回到珍珠港
every other ship on that ocean
那我個人就會要求
I will personally .
桑德斯 我們部門的指揮官
Yo Saunders,ever been in a department run
就像是唐納德·特朗普
by some kind of Donald Trump
和邁克·泰森的突變結合體
Mike Tyson mutant combo
你說什麼? 雷克斯士官
What was that petty officer Raikes?
沒說什麼 長官
Nothing,sir
我聽到你說唐納德·特朗普
I swear you said Donald Trump
我說得對嗎?
Wanna calrify?
我還聽到你說邁克·泰森
I think I heard a Myke Tyson as well.
我的意思是你和泰森一樣
If you did,it was only in reference to the fact the you
都擁有強健的體魄
project great physical intensity
謝謝抬舉
That's flattering
霍伯 有架直升機要過來
Hopper! A heel headed for the Samson.
你給我坐上去
Make sure your ass is on it.
- 為什麼? - 我怎麼知道
- Why? - I don't know why
- 只管坐上去就是了 - 是
- Just make sure your on it!- Copy sir.
倒霉!
Damn!
我們已從約翰·保羅·瓊斯號起飛
we has taken off from John Paul Jones
正將霍伯上尉帶往桑普森號
Lt Hopper is on board
軍法署打來電話
I just got off the phone with the JAG
怎麼了?
And?
他們準備開除你
They are probably gonna kick you out of the Navy
什麼時候?
When?
回去的時候
The day we get back
演習結束那天? - 對
From Rimpac? - Yeap
你得幫我打電話求求情
You've gotta make some calls
打電話?
Some calls?
事到如今讓我跟誰求情?
Who do I call to teach you humility?
對不起 我沒有電話號碼
I'm sorry,I dont' have that number
我真是想不通
I just don't get it man.
你有很大的潛力
You got so much potential
對不起讓你為難了
I'm sorry you have to deal with this
抱歉讓你失望了
And I'm sorry I let you down
海軍理療實驗室 夏威夷 歐湖島
把注意力放在綠色標記上
Stand up nice and tall I want you to focus on that green marker right
你以為我把注意力放在哪兒?
Where do you think I'm paying attention to?
我的腳沒法再併攏了
My feet can't get any closer
抬頭挺胸!
Stand up tall!
行了 我受夠了
Alright,I've had enough of this
加油 再堅持一會兒
Keep going.Just a little more
快把這玩意兒關了
Turn the damn thing off!
別這樣 就快成功了
Come on,we're just about there.
快把它關掉!
Turn it off now!
我是你的新理療師
I'm your new physical therapist.
我感覺你有怨氣
I'm sensing alot of anger
你真是明察秋毫
Very persceptive of you
除了怨氣還有別的情緒嗎? 米克
Is there anything besides anger in there,Mick?
基本沒有
Not much
你原來的理療師
Your last therapist
說你喪失鬥志了 是這樣嗎?
says that you lost the will to fight Is that accurate?
我的腿都沒了還能有什麼鬥志?
I lost my fight when I lost my legs
還記得嗎?
You realise
你二十二歲就拿到了“金手套獎”
you're still the same man that won the Golden Gloves
還在阿富汗拿到了銅星勛章
at 22,Bronze Star in Afganistan?
我是個殘廢
I'm half a man
殘廢人是沒法打仗的
and half a man ain't enough to be a soldier
而我只會打仗
That's all I've ever known.
行了 我們走!
Alright.Let's go!
我們出去散散步
We're gonna take a walk
我不去
No we're not!
戴上腿
Legs on!
你說不想爬山 可你爬得很好
You're doing pretty good for a guy who doesn't wanna be hiking
我的狗 "芥末" 都能爬這山
My dog Mustard would climb this mountain.
好啊 你可以和 "芥末" 一起去
Great you and Mustard can go
爬莫納克亞山 會很開心的
you can make some memories of Mt.Kaia,sounds like fun
它死了 被卡車撞死了
Mustard's dead.He got hit by a dump truck
對不起
Sorry.
沒關係
I'm over it
我還以為你那兒沒信號
Hey.I thought you would be out of range by now?
還有五分鐘就沒信號了
I have around five minutes left
怎麼樣?  - 挺好的
How is it? - It's fine.
對不起 我搞砸了
I'm sorry.I messed up
等我一回來我就去找你爸談
And I'm going to talk to your father as soon as I get back
這次別再搞砸了 好嗎?
Stop messing things up,ok?
明白 我愛你
Copy that.I love you
我愛你
I love you
怎麼了? 帕克
What is it Parker?
來看看這個
Take a look at this
追蹤五個外來目標
有意思 開玩笑吧?
Nice one.It's a joke right?
我不這麼想
I don't think so.
天哪!
My God!
夏威夷  燈塔
數據站 鞍嶺站
卡爾!
Cal!
雷達屏上有奇怪的活動物體
I got some weird activity on all the radar screens
奇怪嗎?
Weird?
是的 非常奇怪
Yeah,man really weird
諾格萊迪博士打電話找你
Oh,arg,Dr Nogrady is on the phone for you too
這太奇怪了
That is weird
諾格萊迪博士找我
Seriously? Dr.Nogrady
麻煩你下次先說這個 好嗎? 丹尼
Lead with that next time okay,Danny
你得先說重要的事情
You gotta start prioritising your information
如果你要跟我說數字
You gotta tell me "1,2,3"
就別說字母 懂嗎?
you don't start with "n".Know what i mean?
我不是要說你笨
I'm not saying your a boob
不過你做出來的事真的很笨
but his is like boobish behavior.
嗨 諾格萊迪博士!
Hi,Dr Nogrady!
你看到了嗎?
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
你說有外來信號?
The incoming tracks
沒錯
Correct
我看到五個清晰物體
I've got 5 distinct objects
五個清晰物體在以編隊的形式移動
distinct objects.that are moving in formation
它們在追蹤我的信號
They're locked in on my signal
正在朝我這兒來
They're headed straight for me
是的
Correct.
也許我們該聯繫宇航局
Uh maybe we should call NASA
宇航局知道了 他們已經在線上了
NASA have called us.They're on the phone right now.
早上好 薩帕塔先生
Good morning,Mr Sabata.
宇航局?
NASA?
我們在追蹤從主體上分裂下來的物體
We're tracking something splitering off from the main group
我覺得那不是分裂
That's not splitting off
那東西是在解體
That thing is breaking apart
有人問過中國方面嗎?
Has anyone called the Chinese.
會不會是他們的東西?
Because this is no meteor
是的 我們問過了
Yes.We've checked
不是中國 也不是俄羅斯的
It's not the Russians,it's not the Chinese
也許我們該通知空軍
Maybe we should call the Air Force
讓他們準備好戰鬥機
because they might wanna fuel up their jets
空軍官員也在線上
The Air Force is on the line
那個東西正在朝你那邊過去
It appears the event is headed your way
你做好準備
Prepare yourself!
我明白
Roger that.
你說我該怎麼準備呢? 長官
How would you suggest that I prepare myself sir?
打起精神
Brace!
中國 香港
各位請坐
Let's all be seated
誰能跟我解釋一下現在的情況?
I'm hoping somebody here can explain this to me.
部長先生 五個不明物體中
Mr.Secretary.Four of the five objects landed
有四個落在太平洋
in the Pacific Ocean
第五個裂成了碎片
The fifth one appeared to have broken apart
對中國香港造成了巨大影響
we're making significant contact with Hong Kong
其他地區也受到了影響
But other places were also affected
蘇格蘭 德國 法國 甚至愛荷華州
Scotland,Germany,France ,even Iowa
是什麼東西?
So what is it?
這個我們目前還不能確定
Well sir,at this point we're working on a couple theories
請問你是誰?
And you are whom sir?
我是宇航局的
I'm with NASA.
為什麼宇航局的人會來?
Well what is NASA present in this room for?
這很可能是一次正式的外星接觸
We're looking at the very real possibility
我們認為該物體來自格利澤星系
It this is legitimate extrateristrial contact
也就是G行星所在的星系
appears that it originated from Gliese solar system Home of Planet G
你是說我們向太空發信號
You are saying that we sent out a signal
然後就收到外星人的回應了?
and we got back an alien response?
長官 基地發來消息
Sir,we just got word from Pearl
他們認為影響香港的不明物體
They believe whatever made impact with Hong Kong
也影響到太平洋
has also made impact with the Pacific Ocean
太平洋哪裡?
Where in the Pacific?
距離我們現在的位置向南大約
Aproximately 150 miles south of where
一百五十海里的地方
we are right now sir
應該就在那兒 可我們沒找到
It should be right there but we're not seeing anything
聯繫桑普森號 - 是 長官
Get me the Samson - ye sir
基準航向二二零 航速二十五節
Base course 2-2-0.Speed 25
上校
Captain
得到普森號號命令讓我們組成一號編隊
Samson has ordered us to change course to Formation One
標準舵 保持航向二二零
standard rudder,keep course 2-2-0
這裡是妙高號確認
there's Myoko Confirm
我們已經收到傷亡報告
As casualty reports come in
但還不清楚對香港造成破壞的是什麼東西
it is still unclear exactly what it was that hit Hong Kong
現在還不清楚那是什麼東西
Now it's not entirely clear what is that
人們看到天空中有火焰
People See the fire in air.
但沒有人知道那是什麼
but no one knows what they are
這不是地球上的東西
It isn't anything from this planet
你怎麼知道?
How do we know that?
中國人已經對它取樣了
Because the Chinese have sampled it
它的材料在元素週期表上不存在
It's made of a material that doesn't exist in the periodic table
也就是說不是從地球上來的
It's literally not of this earth!
他們唯一識別出的元素是鐒
The only element they've been able to identify is Lawrensium
鐒元素?
Lawrensium?
別抖腳了
You gotta stop tapping!
你也在抖 你抖得更厲害
You're tapping,your're the loud one!
從形狀上看
Looking at the grid patterns
有點像太陽能電池板
it's something in the neighborhood of solar paneling
或者是通信板
communications paneling
可能是某種通信裝置
Maybe some kind of communication unit.
通信裝置?
Communications?
他們要和誰通信?
Who's communicating what?And to who?
那是什麼玩意兒?
What the heck is that?
駕駛台 我是右舷瞭望
Hey bridge starboard lookout
我在水面上發現不明物體
We've got an unknown surface contact bearings
方位二三二 距離八千碼
2-3-2 true approximately 8,000 yards
長官 - 幹嗎?
Sir! - Yeap.
請您過來看一下
You may wanna come take a look at this
我正看著呢 大副
I am looking at it Mr.Strogo
雷達上面有點奇怪
On the radar sir.Something very peculiar.
這是約翰·保羅·瓊斯號?
That's the John Paul Jones right?
是的
Yes sir
這是妙高號? - 沒錯
Myoko? - Yes sir it is.
那玩意兒在哪兒?
Why don't i see.see that?
戰情中心 我看到追蹤目標
Combat Captain.I need visual on the bearing
在水平位置二三七 雷達上有嗎?
2-3-7 on the horizon What do you hold a that bearing?
我在雷達上沒有找到
Birdge T.O,I've got nothing at 2-3-7.
我用眼睛都能看到 你再找找
I'm looking right at it Mr.Hopper.Find me something
觀測器 二三七 有東西嗎?
Scope! 2-3-7.What've we got?
稍等 那裡什麼也沒有
Stand by.Negative sir.Scope's clear.I got nothing.
雷達是不是被你弄壞了?
Taylor,did you break this son of a bitch?
沒有 我沒有動過它
No sir.I didn't do anything to it sir.
要是被你弄壞了我宰了你
You know I'll throw your ass of this ship?
我知道你會的
I know you will sir
找到了 我這裡有
I got something sir.On my camera.
是什麼?
What is it?
不知道
I don't know?
這是演習項目嗎?
Is this some kind of exercise.
有可能
Probably.
發現不明船體大約在15度方向
Unknown vessel in the vicinity of 1-5 degrees
北37分 159度 西33分
37 minutes north,1-5-9 degrees 3-3 minutes west
請通過甚高頻頻道16與我們聯繫
Requesting status communication on my vessel on VFH channel 16
表明你的身份 完畢
and identify yourself.Over
約翰·保羅·瓊斯號
John Paul Jones
我是桑普森號指揮官
this Samson,Charlie Oscar
收到 有什麼事?
John Paul Jones Charlie Oscar
我要你派個小隊到那邊看看
I'ld like you to send a team over and take a closer look
沒問題 我馬上派人過去
No problem.We'll get a team in the water right away
收到 夥計們
Roger.Tell you what boys
我感覺情況很複雜
This is a head stomper.
這是什麼? 丟失的中國貨物嗎?
What is it?A box of cargo? Chinese?
不知道
I don't know?
遊艇?
A yatch?
衛星?
A satellite?
比斯特 我之前不知道它是什麼
Beast,I didn't know 5 seconds ago
現在也不知道
and I don't know now
這裡是美國海軍戰艦
This is the US Navy Warship
約翰·保羅·瓊斯號
John Paul Jones
我要跟你們通話
I'm attempting to communicate with you
我們要登船了
Prepare to be boarded.
你見過這種東西嗎?
You ever seen anything like this?
沒有
No
很奇怪
Weird man
上尉 我覺得這不是個好主意
L.T! I don't think that's a good idea!
收到 軍士長
Got it chief!
上尉 別去碰它
Real bad idea lieutenant!
見鬼
Oh shit!
雷克斯 快救他
Move it Raikes!
上尉 快上來
L.T!Lieutenant get up!
上尉
Lieutenant!
哇哇哇哇哦!
Wow wow woohoo!
長官
Sir!
接桑普森號
Get me the Samson.
桑普森號 這裡是總部
Alfa-Bravo,Samson,this is  Alfa-Bravo!
長官 聯繫不上桑普森號
Sir we're not able to contact the Samson.
控制台 這裡是 馴馬人四零四
Control,this is Rough Rider 404
我這裡受到嚴重干擾
Encountering some suspicious
馴馬人四零四 請回話
Rough Rider 4-0-4,come in? Do you copy?
立即進入一級戰備
Get the force at weapons pos 1.
紅色警報 一級戰備
Warning red.Weapons tight
所有武器備便
I want everything loaded.
駕駛台 出了什麼事?
bridge What's happened?
長官 我們的雷達壞了
My radar's closing down sir!
我們和基地失去聯繫
We've lost contact with base
我告訴你 那是朝鮮人的
It's the North Koreans,I'm telling ya
霍伯上尉 你沒事吧?
Lieutenant,you good?
跟我說話啊?
Come on,you wit me?
發動啊!
come on!
該死的!
Dammit!
說話 你沒事吧?
Come on! Squared away?
我沒事
Squared away.
那個玩意兒把電池弄壞了
Whatever that thing is,killed the battery
快想辦法 比斯特!
Come on,Beast!
那是什麼?
What is that?
情況不妙
That's not dead.
那到底是什麼?
What the hell is that?
我從沒見過這種東西
I've never seen this
你覺得這會不會是
Do you think this could be some
海軍演習的什麼秘密行動?
super secret navy surprise exercise?
如果是的話
Coz if so
他們搞得也太誇張了吧
they've gone way too far
天哪
What the.
向他們鳴笛警告
Let's give them a warning Helmsman.
是 長官
Aye aye sir
這到底是什麼?
What the hell is this?
我參軍可不是為了這個!
I didn't sign up for this bullshit!
當然不是
No shit dude!
通訊系統中斷 兩分鐘後恢復
Com stats are offline,Should be back up in 2 minutes!
收到
Copy that
給約翰·保羅·瓊斯號發信號
Signal to John Paul Jones
鳴槍警告 第一輪
Fire a warning shot.One round
十發 打左側位置
10 mil,left offense
五十一號遙控炮塔 火炮射擊準備
Battey mount 51 in remote
五十一號炮塔準備完畢
Battey mount 51 Ready
我們要打誰?
Who we shooting at?
我不知道
I do not know
快開船 比斯特!
Let's move it,Beast!
船動不了
It's dead in the water.
奧蒂 給我到下風舵去 - 是 長官!
Ort,get your ass up.- Yes sir!
開火!
Fire!
炮彈來了
Incoming headed
朝約翰·保羅·瓊斯號去了
for the John Paul Jones!
正在逼近 水平位置
Unknown inbound!
使用近程防禦武器系統
Rampart! Kill it with CWIS
這算是什麼狗屁導彈...
What kind of tough...
甲板上有人嗎?
Were there men out on the bridge?
是的 長官!
Yes sir,there were!
行了 總算發動了
Firing it up
回船上去
back now
長官!
Sir!
幹掉它
Fire!
霍伯到底想幹什麼?
What the hell is Hopper doing?
所有引擎全速航行!
All engines ahead!
是 所有引擎全速航行!
All engines ahead! Aye sir!
戰情中心報告說相控陣雷達
Sir,CIC reports both
和火控雷達都無法追蹤目標
spy and fire patrol radar cannot lock on
開火!
Fire!
戰情中心 開火!
CIC,fire!
右邊有炮彈!
Incoming on the way!
炮彈來了
Incoming headed
我們中彈了
We're hit!
長官 船體進水了
Sir,we have a hull breach!
舵手 快回駕駛艙
Helmsman get back on the helm!
是 長官!
Aye sir!
繼續開火 - 是
Rapid contingent fire! - Sir!
不
Nooo!!!
操
Damn!
送我去約翰·保羅·瓊斯號!
Get me to the John Paul Jone!
快!
Now!
敵人保持防禦陣形
Targets are holding defensive formation
布勞利上校在哪兒?
Where's the captain?Where is he?
出了什麼事?
What happened?
布勞利和穆勒納羅都死了
Captain and XO (Executive Officer) are dead!
什麼?
What?
都死了!
They're dead!
艦長和副艦長都死了
CO and XO are dead!
那誰在指揮?
Who's in charge?
這兒誰軍銜最高?
Who's next fall senior?
你
You are.
現在你是艦長
It's your ship sir
你軍銜最高 長官
You're senior officer,sir
長官 請趕快下命令吧
Sir if you would please just give me an order
我不知道該幹什麼
i don't know what to do sir
我們衝過去
We're going in
全力進攻
Full attack
這就是命令
That's an order
進攻嗎? -- 是的
Attack sir? - Yes!
你要我下命令 這就是命令
You wanted an order! That's an order!
快去吧!
Let's go!
你聽到了?
You heard him?
是 長官!
Aye aye sir!
所有炮火準備
Ready all guns.
火控系統故障 需要三分鐘恢復
Firing tools are offline.I need three minutes
告訴永田 他來不來我都要打
Tell Nagata I'm going with or without him.
他瘋了!
This is crazy!
他需要支援!
He needs help!
長官 確定要攻擊嗎?
Sir you really want to attack this thing?
是的 我確定!
Yes,yes i do!
給我開火!
Get ready to fire!
長官 妙高號被擊中
Myoko is hit sir!
武器準備好了嗎?
Are the weapons ready?
開火的船都被擊毀了
Sir they've killed everything that's fired on them
準備攻擊 我們要衝過去
Get the guns online and we ram this thing!
那玩意殺了我哥哥和他的船員
They killed my brother and every man on his ship.
長官 現在我們沒有武器
We have no weapons to attack with sir
設定航向為三一零
Then set course to 3-1-0
這是碰撞航向 你瘋了嗎? - 三一零
That's a collision course! - 3-1-0!!!
水裡有妙高號的船員
Sir,there are sailors in the water!
做好準備 我們要撞爛它
Get the guns online and we're gonna ram this thing!
妙高號在下沉 求你了 長官
Sir,the Myoko is sinking.Sir please!
設定航向為三一零 - 求你了 長官!
Set the course to 3-1-0! -  Sir please!
水裡還有船員 他們都會死的
There are sailors in the water sir!
右滿舵
Hard starboard.
是 右滿舵
Hard starboard,aye sir.
把船員救上來 - 是 長官!
Get them outta the water - Yes sir
怎麼回事?
What's happening?
到底怎麼回事?
What the hell's happening?
他們為什麼不攻擊我們了?
Why aren't they attacking?
那是外星人嗎?
Are those things aliens!?
你就不能閉上嘴嗎?
Would you please shut up!
通知基地派航母過來
We need help
現在誰在指揮? - 霍伯
Who's running this ship!? - Hopper
你開玩笑嗎?
Yo are you kidding me?
霍伯怎麼能指揮? 簡直是胡鬧
Hopper's running the ship?This is bullshit!
我們死定了
We're all gonna die!
那是什麼鬼東西?
What the hell are those things!?
那到底是什麼玩意兒?
What is that thing!?
美國海軍陸戰隊基地 夏威夷 歐湖島 卡內奧赫灣
通訊都中斷了 你有信號嗎?
communications shut down! do you copy?
所有頻率都沒有信號
all frequency communications interruption
見鬼
Oh shit!
趕快撤離
Just get out of here
我們要墜毀了!
We're going down!
好球
strike
爸爸
Dad
長官 我無法解釋
Sir,I can't explain this
我們和屏障另一邊的人
We've lost communication with everyone
完全失去聯繫了
on the otherside of the barrier
我們進不去 他們也出不來
We can't get in and they can't get out.
那片屏障式的區域
The field,whatever it is
它的高度達到三十萬英尺
it extends about 300,000 feet in altitude
深度大約有兩海里
and has depth of about 2 nautical miles
太平洋艦隊的謝恩上將報告說
we are in contact with Admiral Shane of the Pacific fleet
我們的艦隊都被隔在那片區域外
but right now our navy is effectively trapped outside the area
裡面沒我們的人嗎?
So we have nobody in there?
我們有三艘導彈驅逐艦困在裡面
Well sir,we have 3 guided missile destroyers still unaccounted for
這些人也算是戰鬥力吧
So it's conceivable we do have somebody inside
誰?
Well who?
上校
Captain! Captain!
這些都是你造成的 你看見了嗎?
it was all your fault Did you see that?
你這混蛋
you fucking asshole
行了  我們走
All right Let's go.
堅持住! 沒事的 我們快走!
hang on! it is all right.Let's go.
連我奶奶都能爬這山
My grandmother could climb this mountain
才剛開始呢 米克
It's a start Mick
那是什麼?
What was that?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
你們在這兒幹什麼?
What are you guys doing up here?
趕快下山去 快走
I need you to get off this mountain right now.
出了什麼事?
Wait,what's going on? Why?
歐湖島遭到襲擊
The island's under attack
被誰襲擊了?
Attack,by who?
不知道 聽說好像是外星人
I don't know.People are using the word "alien"
外星人?
Aliens?
我不知道
We don't know
反正海軍陸戰隊基地
hatever it is took out the Marine base
和到這兒的路都被毀了
all roads leading to this mountain have been destroyed
手機 無線電 網絡
Cellphones,radio,internet
所有通訊都中斷了
Everything is shut down
海軍已經在海岸邊集結了
The Navy's engaged just off from the coast
海軍?
The Navy?
你們趕緊下山吧
I need you and your friend off of this mountain right now
我們走! 維克
Come on,let's go! Vic
把車留在這兒 我們去封路
leave your car here.It'll block the road
你要去哪兒?
Where you going?
米克 你上哪兒去?
Mick! Where are you going?
我從來沒見過外星人
I ain't ever seen an alien
你見過外星人嗎?
Have you ever seen an alien?
米克! 別丟下我
Mick!Don't leave me alone
你看到嗎? 那是什麼?
Woah sole! What the hell was that?
文斯 你看到了嗎?
Hey Fizz,did you see that?
好像是飛機 我從來沒有...
Looked like a jet Well I ain't never...
長官 我們需要你
Sir,we need you
你得來指揮
We need you now
我不行
I can't
如果你不行?
If you can't?
還有誰行?
Who can?
艦長
Captain
在哪兒找到的?
Where did we find it?
他們的運輸機在去歐湖島時墜毀了
One of their transporters must have crashed over the island.
到處是殘骸
There was debris everywhere
是托馬斯和波茨用抓勾
Thomas and Potts just fished him right
把這傢伙從海里撈上來的
outta the water with a grappling hook
我跟他們說這樣不好
Look I told them it was a bad idea
可他們不聽
but they kept yanking and i kept telling them no
見鬼
shit!
該死的
Oh damn!
給我手電筒
Beast flashlight
我爸一直說外星人會來
My dad said they'ld come He said it my whole life
他說一定有外星人
He said we ain't alone
不是我們找到他們
He said one day we'll find them
就是被他們找到
or they'll find us
知道他還說了什麼嗎?
Know what else he said?
他說...
He said...
但願那天來的時候他已經死了
I hope I ain't around when that day comes
他還沒死
That is not dead!
我有一種不祥的預感
I've got a bad feeling about this
什麼不祥預感?
What bad feeling?
這種感覺就像“我們需要一個新的星球
Like we're gonna need a new planet kind of bad feeling
C52需要醫療救援 兩人受傷
Medical casualty.C-53 2 men down
他們還在船上
It's still on the ship
封鎖出入口
Lock down the ship!
大家都沒事吧?
Is everyone alright?
所有人都在嗎?
Is everyone accounted for?
第四層有動靜
Just heard something on level 4
雷克斯 上去
Raikes,up
快走!
Move! Move!
你看到嗎?
What do you see?
有外星人嗎?
Do you see it?
沒有長官!
No sir!
什麼也沒有  沒有
I've got nothing sir!
他怎麼樣?
How is he?
傷得很重 很糟糕
Not good sir! Not good!
你們倆送他去治療室
You two,get him to medical now!
雷克斯 你跟我來
Raikes,you're with me!
快離開這兒!
Get outta here!
不!
no!
喂!
Yo! Hey!
雷克斯!
Raikes!
你去戰情中心 快去!
Get your ass to CIC!Now!
來吧!
Come on!
雷克斯 但願你到了!
Raikes,you better be there!
快點
Come on,come on.
去死吧 混蛋!
Mahalo mother...!
我們得趕快下山
We gotta get off this mountain.
那個警察身上有車鑰匙
The cop left the keys on his belt
你去把它拿來
You gotta go down and get em
你能行的
You can do it
快過來
Now!
緊急呼叫!
This is an emergency call!
有人聽見嗎?
Can anyone hear me?
通訊檢查!
Radio check!
有人聽見嗎? 完畢
Can anyone hear me? Over.
等等 別走
Wait up! Wait up don't leave
站住別動! 別開槍!
Stop right there!Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
你是誰?
Who are you?
我是卡爾·薩帕塔 我是...
I'm Cal Zapata! We sent out a beacon...
見鬼! 他是機器人嗎?
Oh shit! Is he a cyborg!?
你們和外星人是一夥的?
Are you guys with them?
如果你是人類 能不能把槍放下?
He's human.Can you please put the gun down?
米克! 把槍放下
Mick! Put your gun down.
我告訴過他們外星人會入侵
I told them something like this could happen
就像哥倫布發現新大陸
I said it was gonna be like Columbus and the Indians
我們就是印第安人
conquistadors and incas
可他們說不會的 外星人很友善
they said no it'll be sweet.
外星人殺了我的助手
They killed my grad students
行了! 冷靜點!
Ok! Calm down!
我喘不過氣了...
I can't...
呼吸 深呼吸
Slow.Slow.
坐下來 沒事的 深呼吸
Sit down! Slow breaths
你嚇到他了 米克!
You're freaking him out,Mick!
這傢伙也太容易被嚇到了
I doubt it takes much to freak him out.
我們需要海軍陸戰隊
We need the marines,we need the army
陸軍 空軍 所有部隊
We need all of them
我們認為那個落在香港的
It is the strong belief of the Chinese that what crashed into Hong Kong
不明物體可能是某種通信船
was some sort of communications ship
你是說一部會飛的電話掉下來
So you're saying a flying telephone cratered
害死了兩萬五千人?
and took out 25,000 people
我的意思是這些外星人好像急於
What I'm saying is that our visitors seem
要和他們自己的星球取得聯繫
extrodinarily concerned with establishing a line of communication home
既然他們的通信船沒了
If they've lost their communications ship
那怎麼聯繫? 用我們的設備?
how could they do that?The same way we did
我們在夏威夷有個上行數據站
Our communications station in Hawaii has
能通過陸地衛星七號
the ability to send a message to deep space
向外太空發送信號
by the LandSat 7 satellite
我想他們就是為了這個占領那兒的
I believe it's for that asset they've domed the island
他們的目的可能是毀滅全人類
We're looking at a extinction level event
所有軍事行動最關鍵的一步
The most critical part of any military operation
就是建立通信
to establish communications
這樣就能呼叫增援和後續部隊
reinforcements,rescue organization
你說外星人想打電話回家?
Are you saying ET wants to phone home?
那實在是太可怕了
That would be incredibly.incredibly bad
現在只有五艘外星飛船來到地球
I mean so far only 5 ships have made contact
如果五艘船可以
If 5 ships could do this
那五十艘 五百艘 五千艘
what do you think 50 could do or 500 or 5000
五十萬艘都能來
or 500,000?
長官 您能不能聽我說句話?
Sir,if I could just have a minute?
只要一小會兒
Just give me one second
你給我看蜥蜴幹嘛?
Why am I staring at a lizard?
這是我的寵物 佩內洛普三世
Coz this is my pet lizard sir,Penelope the Third
然後呢?
And?
外星人的眼睛和蜥蜴一樣
They have the exact same eyes
給你十五秒 快說
You've got 15 seconds.Go
長官 我戴了頭盔
Ok,so I put the helmet on
外星人的頭盔就像太陽眼鏡
the helmet is just basically extreme sunglasses
另外有些水合作用
and some hydration
氧飽和之類的 這個我不太懂
some oxygen and bunch of other stuff I don't understand
有一次我帶佩內洛普去海灘
We took Penelope to the beach one time
那簡直糟透了 它變得很狂躁
Which was a terrible idea.She went absolutely crazy
因為它怕陽光
because she couldn't handle the sunlight
我覺得那些外星人也怕陽光
you see.I don't think they can handle the sunlight either
你還試過別的嗎?
Did you try anything else on?
沒有 長官 只有頭盔
Negative,sir.Just the helmet
重要新聞
科學家已經確認有一架飛碟
Scientist have confirmed that there was a UFO
停在靠近夏威夷海岸的太平洋上
landing in the Pacific Ocean,off the coast of Hawaii
今天我要告訴美國人民
Today I want to update the American people
夏威夷地區局勢的最新情況
on what we know about the situation in Hawaii
首先我們已經盡一切所能提供支援
First we are bringing all available resources.
情況非常嚴峻
全世界的希望都寄託在這三艘軍艦上
自從那個奇怪的裝置啟動後
這三艘軍艦就與外界失去了聯繫
這起事件造成了全球範圍的恐慌
各地出現了前所未有的混亂局面
The news has sparked global unrest among the population
許多國家的政府宣布進入緊急狀態
nleashing and unprecedented wave of chaos across the world
你讓飛機盡快起飛
Scramble the jets admiral!
我們要派人衝進去
We need to get in there!
我比你更清楚也更想衝進去
I'm far more aware than you of the need to get inside there
可現在去就是送死
But wasting more lives will not help
要我再派一架飛機嗎?
Want me to send another plane?
只要你來當副駕駛
I'll do it the second you sit
我馬上就派飛機進去!
your ass in the co-pilot seat,sir!
他們在發信號嗎?
Are they transmitting?
有可能 不過現在發了沒用
They could be,but it wouldn't do them any good.
這裡沒有能接收信號的衛星
There's no satellite to receive the transmission
我們只有陸地衛星七號
We beam to LandSat 7.
陸地衛星七號是什麼?
What's Landsat 7 ?
一顆深太空衛星
It's a deep space satellite
每隔二十四小時在軌進行一次運行
It only orbits into range once,every 24 hours
衛星什麼時候會就位?
When's the satellite in position?
早上八點四十三分
8:43 AM.
還有五個小時他們就能用衛星
We got about 5 hours and they'll use it
發射他們的信號
to slingshot their transmission
發射到哪裡?
Slingshot where?
不知道 他們來的地方吧
I don't know.Whereever it is they're from
珍珠港在這兒
Pearl Harbor here
我們大概在這兒
We're approximately here
而那些外星人應該在這當中
And they,whatever they are,they're somewhere in the middle
我們被困住了
We're trapped in here.
除非我們能用肉眼看到
What we know right now is we can't
否則就沒法瞄準他們
target them unless we have a plain line of sight.
沒有雷達就沒法追蹤他們 對嗎?
Without radar we have no way to track them Correct?
沒錯
Correct.
不過我覺得他們也看不見我們
But I don't think they can see us either
為什麼? - 否則我們早就死了
Why? -- Because we are still alive
也就是說我們互相都看不見
Ok! So they can't see us and we can't see them
沒辦法在防區外攻擊他們
we have no way to hit them from a safe distance
有一個辦法
There is a way
什麼辦法?
A way?
看不見卻又看得見
A way of seeing them without seeing them
你要引用《孫子兵法》了 對嗎?
You're going to reference  right now?
你要說的辦法是聲東擊西嗎?
What are suppose to fight the enemy where they aren't?
還是以柔克剛
Move like water?
那本書我讀了六遍 根本沒用
Except I've read that thing like 6 times and it makes no sense
那本書是中國人寫的
That book is Chinese.
反正我看不懂
Still makes no sense
我的辦法要簡單得多
My way is much more simple
我們用它對付美國二十年了
We've been doing it to America for 20 years
追蹤排水量
Water displacement
怎麼追蹤排水量?
How do you track water displacement?
用海嘯預警浮標 - 海嘯預警浮標?
Tsunami buoys.- Tsunami buoys?
島周圍有很多海嘯預警浮標
You have them surrounding the islands
它們會發送排水量數據
transmitting displacement data
我們黑進你們的系統就能看到數據
we hack into the transmissions,form a grid
沒有雷達你沒法追蹤
We can't get anything without radar
不需要雷達
I don't need radar
用無線電頻率就行了
Just the radio frequecies
現在請關掉宙斯盾雷達
Turn off radar please
摩爾軍士長 長官
Chief Moore Sir!
關閉雷達
Secure Spy!
是 關閉雷達
Securing spy sir
顯示海洋局的數據
Display NOAA data
海洋局嗎? - 沒錯
NOAA data? - Yes,correct
聽他的 顯示海洋局的數據
You heard him.display NOAA data
美國國家海洋和大氣管理局
這是什麼?
What the hell is that?
是浮標
It's a buoy
每次被海浪衝擊都會發送一個信號
If it get's hit by a wave,it transmits a signal
顯示信號圖表
Bring up chart block
顯示圖表 快點
Chart block.Bring it up
約翰·保羅·瓊斯號
這樣就能追蹤到他們了
So we can track without radar
我們一般用這個方法應急
We would practice it as a contingency plan
老奸巨猾 卑鄙 無恥
You dirty,cheating,snakey
危險的世界
Rough world
我喜歡
I like it
上校!
Captain!
現在你也是艦長
My chair is your chair sir
我哥哥也會這麼做的
My brother would have done the same
能聯繫上霍伯就好了
How should we get a hold of Hopper
誰是霍伯?
Who's Hopper?
他是一艘伯克級驅逐艦上的武器指揮官
He's the Tactical Actions Officer on an Arleigh Burke class destroyer
他們的驅逐艦有足夠能力炸平這座山
It has the resources that can take this entire mountain out
不錯 是個好主意 快聯繫他
Great.That makes a lot of sense.Let's call him
不行 通訊設備都壞了
We can't.Everything is jammed
外星人在用電磁場屏蔽我們的信號
They're using an electromagnetic field to block our signals
它更像脈衝波 而不是磚
it's more like a pulse,Not a brick wall
它是有縫隙的
There's gaps,ok?
我們還是有可能和外界取得聯繫
From inside the barrier,we might be able to get a call out
只要我能拿到頻譜分析儀
If I could get to my spectrum analyzer then
理論上說我們能找到一個頻率
theoretically we could find a frequency that could broadcast
你是說你有能打電話的設備?
Do you have a piece of equipment that can make a call?
對
Yeah
去拿!
Get it!
不行
Well i can't
它在下面 就在外星人窩裡
because it's down there,in that nest of aliens
你去拿過來
You're gonna go get it
不去
No
去
Yes
我們要找出排水量的規律
We are looking for patterns of water displacement
這個浮標在水下
That bouy's underwater
那是艘船
That's a ship
準備攻擊 - 是
Get on your gun - Sir
目標 E11
Target Echo 1-1
收到 E11
Roger.Echo 1-1
準備開火
Ready to fire
一開火就會暴露我們的位置
When we fire,they will know where we are
開火!
Fire!
奧蒂 打中了嗎?
Orly,anything?
沒有 長官
Negative,sir! It's a miss!
它朝我們過來了!
It's heading towards us!
準備好了嗎?
You ready?
對不起
I'm sorry
我是絕對不會到那下邊去的
there's no possible way I'm going down there
我可不想逞什麼英雄
I don't posses that kind of courage
你要麼壯起膽子下去
Right now you're going to acquire that courage
要麼我就用這鋼腿踢爛你的屁股
I'm going to break my steel leg off of your ass
聽明白了嗎?
You feel me?
明白
I feel you
行了 快去!
Go! Now!
勇敢點兒
Acquiring courage
怎麼了?
What?
目標F24
Foxtrot 2-4
收到 F24
準備就緒  - 開火
Ready to fire - Fire
奧蒂 打中了嗎?
Orly,anything?
沒有 長官
Negative,sir
我覺得這主意糟透了
Stupid ninkumpoop idea
又來了一艘!
There's another one!
炮彈來了!
Incoming! Incoming!
是從兩個方向來的
Sir they're coming from both directions!
全速倒車
Engines! Back full!
炮彈來了
Incoming!
目標 I37!
India 3-7!
收到 I37!
裝彈完畢!
Loaded!
第二個坐標 R26
Second coordinates! Romeo 2-6.
導彈準備完畢 隨時可以發射
Sir,we're hot over here! Missiles good to go
我們開火吧 永田上校!
Let's light em up Cpt Nagata!
永田上校!
Captain Nagata!
開火!
Fire!
太棒了 打中了
Holy shit! Hit
乾得好 太棒了
Hit sir! Hit!
有人能聽到嗎?
Any station hear us?
這裡呼叫援助!
This is a call for help!
如果有軍艦 警察或者軍人
Any warship or any military personnel
請回答 完畢
please respond Over
這裡是約翰·保羅·瓊斯號
This is the USS John Paul Jones
報告你的身份和位置! -  霍伯!
Identify yourself and your position! - Hopper! Hopper!
薩姆?
Sam?
你沒事吧? 你在哪兒?
Are you okay? Where are you?
謝天謝地 我沒事
I'm ok
外星人在鞍嶺數據站 聽到了嗎?
They are here at the satellite array at Saddle Ridge Do you copy?
他們要用衛星發射信號進行通信
They're going to transmit a signal and establish communication
你們要摧毀這些設施
You need to destroy the facility
還剩下四個小時
We have 4 hours.
四個小時 明白
4 hours.I copy
霍伯!
Hopper!
能聽見嗎?
Can you hear me?
寶貝兒! 你趕快離開那兒
Babe! You need to get out of there
霍伯!
Hopper! Hopper!
線路斷了 不行了
They're gone! They're gone
我們快走吧
We better get gone too
我在想象一艘伯克級驅逐艦
I'm thinking an Arleigh Burke class destroyer's
把這座山炸平的樣子
about to rain hell on this mountain top
我們再幹掉一艘
You ready to kill another one?
T19
Tango 1-9!
T19 裝彈
Tango 1-9! Loaded
W25
Whisky 2-5!
雷克斯 你能追蹤到他們的船嗎?
Raikes,can you get a track on the ship?
不行 它的航向很隨意
Negative.It's moving all over the place
找不到規律
I can't get a line on it
它在水裡亂竄
Sucker's really jumping around
他們很聰明
Very intelligent
離天亮還有多久?  - 40分鐘 長官
What time is sunrise? - 40 minutes,sir
帶這些混蛋去他們不想去的地方
Let's take these bastards somewhere they don't wanna go
戰鬥警報 全體船員 請立即進入戰位
ALl hands to battle stations ready
繞著這裡轉圈 船能保持穩定嗎
I need to know when we round this point if we're gonna hold it tight
就繞著鑽石頭火山
Right around Diamond Head here
那邊的洋流很急
There's a brutal current there
船到那裡肯定會觸礁的
It'll take a miracle to keep her off the reef
奧蒂 你覺得呢? 你能行嗎?
Orly,Is it possible? Can you do it?
也不是不可能
It's not impossible,
我能試試 不過我不知道..
Sir.I can try.But I don't know.
行還是不行?
Can you do it? Yes or no?
目標在七英里外 向我們靠近
Contact is 7 miles out and closing fast
是的 我能行
Yes sir,I can do it.
檢查 正常 快走
Checking Normal go
幹掉他們
Destroy them!
上校 你的槍法怎麼樣?
Captain Nagata,how good is your aim?
很好
Excellent
行了 開始行動吧
Alright let's start this turn!
是 長官 左滿舵
Hard left,sir!
情況怎麼樣? 到處是暗礁
Sarge how we doing? We're on the reef!
奧蒂 你靠得太近了 往左點
Orly,you're way too close! Go left!
別緊張
Easy
我們快要觸礁了 奧蒂!
We're about to kiss these rocks,Orly!
奧蒂!
Orly!
你在哪兒學的射擊?
Where did you learn to shoot?
我不知道這個詞用英語怎麼說
I'm not sure how to say in English
夏令陽
Natsu Camp Summer camp
現在呢? - 還是太近
How about now? - Still too tight!
都到淺水區了 拜託 夥計
I can see fish Orly! Come on man!
距離目標還有二十一秒
Contact.ETA 21 seconds
夏令陽
Summer Camp
距離目標七百碼
Contact 700 yards out
是夏令營吧?
Summer camp?
那年我十二歲 還拿了冠軍
Champion! When I was 12
你開玩笑吧?
Are you kidding me?
他們來了
Here we go
聽我指揮
On my mark
三
Three
二
Two
一
One
開火
Light em up!
還有三英里目標將進入射程
3 miles,Saddle Ridge is in range!
武器狀況
Status of guns
他們去彈藥庫把彈藥都搬上來了
Sir they're bringing up all the rounds from lower decks
長官!
Sir!
快離開這兒
Clear the bridge!
快走!
move!
見鬼!
Shit!
不
No
奧蒂 快起來 我們走
Orly! Get up! Let's go!
快走
Go! Go! Go!
船體破裂
the ship broke
船體嚴重破裂 兩名船員受傷
the ship broke 2 crew get injured
快起來!
Stand up! Come on!
棄船 快跳到水裡去
go go jump to the water
快走!
let' go!
快過來 我來拉你
Come on!  I will lift you up
雷克斯 快點
Raikes! Here! Come on!
就快到了 加油
Here! Come on!
快點
Come on!
快點 我們一起跳!
let's go! We have to jump!
那就是約翰·保羅·瓊斯號
That's the John Paul Jones!
那是霍伯的船
That's Hopper
我看到水裡有很多救生艇
I'm seeing a lot of life boats in the water
你說衛星會在三個小時後就位嗎?
You said the satellite will be in position in 3 hours?
對 沒錯
Yeap,that's correct
如果錯過 他們就得等了
So if they miss it,they have to wait
系統很精確 不會錯過的
My uplink never misses It's not gonna miss.
你的車技怎麼樣?
How are your driving skills?
你問這個幹什麼? 我開車糟透了
What do you mean?My driving skills are horrible
我沒問你
Not your driving
薩姆 你的車技怎麼樣?
Sam! How are your driving skills?
很好
Good
我們試試為地球多爭取一天
Let's see if we can't buy the world another day
這話說得真牛
Who talks like that?
快上車吧 我們走
Just get in the vehicle.Let's go.
我才不去呢
I'm not getting in
要去你們自己去
This is your show now
我現在還不想死呢
I don't have a death wish
再見 兩位
Thank you very much Bye everyone
等等 停車
Stop! Stop!
這個是我的
This is my property
我們不能放棄
It doesn't end like this
你想讓我們怎麼辦?霍伯?
What do you want us to do,Hopper?
我們沒有船了
We have no ship left
還有一艘
We have one
我們還有艘戰艦
We've got a battleship
你瘋了嗎?
Are you crazy?
那是博物館
That's a museum
今天不是
Not today.
密蘇裡號
這船有七十年的歷史 早過時了
This ship is 70 years old,It's totally outdated
射控系統還是模擬的
The firing systems are all analog
發動機有十年沒用過了
The engines haven't been started in a decade
估計還能用 可它們是蒸汽動力
Which would be fine except they're steam which
我不知道怎麼發動
I have no idea how to fire up
就算能給我說明書讓我研究幾個月
even if i had a users manual and 6 weeks to go through it all
我們也沒有足夠人手開動它
e still don't have enough crew to fire it up
我不知道你怎麼想? 長官
I don't know what you're thinking,sir
大家沒事吧?
Is everyone alright?
是的 我們沒事
Yes sir.We're okay
你們已經為國家付出了這麼多
You men have given so much to your country
我無權再向你們要求什麼
no-one has the right to ask any of you
可今天我不得不開口
But I'm asking.
你需要什麼?
What do you need son?
我要借這艘船
I need to borrow your boat
孩子!
Son!
長官!
Sir!
你要一直站在那兒看著我嗎?
What the hell you gonna do? Stand there and stare at me?
快去盯著機器!
Get your goddamn eye on that spotter!
是 我這就去
Eye on spotter,sir!
你在驅逐艦上工作是嗎?  - 是的
Been working on a destroyer haven't you?- Yes sir!
想跟老水手學兩招嗎? - 當然!
Are you ready to play with the big boys? - Oh yes sir!
來吧 來搭把手
Come on,we need the help
酷
Awesome
最好把耳朵堵上
Best cover your ears
像新的一樣
Purrs like kitten!
駕駛台 我是主控室
Bridge,Tanker Joe.
八個鍋爐都熱了
I got 8 boilers hot
可以開始行動了 長官
Ready to rock & roll sir!
我們有多少燃料?
How we looking on fuel?
六百長噸 長官
600 long,sir
這些基本夠用了
Just enough for a maintenance run
武器裝備呢?
Ordinance?
能找來的都找來了
I gathered what we can
不過東西不多
it's not much
讓船下水 我們要乾正事了 - 明白
Let's get her to sea.We got work to do! - Roger that
兩車全速前進
All engines ahead flat!
是 兩車全速前進
All engines ahead flat!Aye sir!
能行嗎?
You good?
行啊 沒問題
Good sir! Good sir!
很好
Good.
一號炮塔?
Status at turret 1?
主炮塔準備完畢
Turret,barrel,armed!
停下
stop
安全
clear
過來搭把手
Come over a hand
二號炮塔?
Status at Turret 2?
右舷炮塔準備完畢
Armed!
三號炮塔?
Status at Turret 3?
左舷炮塔準備完畢
Ready to rock & roll!
準備完畢
Port side armed
長官 我們真的要打歐湖島嗎?
Sir,are we really firing on Oahu?
一點兒沒錯
Sure looks that way
太棒了
Holy shit
鞍嶺五分鐘內進入射程範圍
Saddle Ridge will be in weapons range in 5 minutes
讓那些外星混蛋見鬼去吧
Whoa brother.Somebody's gonna kiss the donkey
霍伯!
Hopper!
我記得它原來不在這兒啊
I didn't think that one moved
我也是
Me neither
我的天哪!你和我開玩笑嗎?
My God! Are you kidding me?
《孫子兵法》
火力指揮 武器情況
Fire control,weapons status
已瞄準目標
Aimed at target
所有炮塔都瞄準二一零
Train all three turrets to 2-1-0
可是長官 這個方向不對
Sir that's the wrong direction
我知道 雷克斯!
I'm well aware of that,Raikes!
他到底想幹嗎?
What the hell's he doing?
他準是瘋了 又瘋了
Losing his mind all over again
左滿舵!
Hard left rudder!
是 左滿舵!
Hard left,aye sir!
拋左舷錨! - 什麼?
Draw port anchor! - What?
趕快拋!
Drop it now!
我們死定了!
We're gonna die!
我們都會死!
We are gonna die!
你會死 我會死
You're gonna die.I'm gonna die.
我們都會死
We're all gonna die.
但今天不會
Just not today
讓那些混蛋吃點兒子彈..
Let's drop some lead on those mother..
開火!
hit it!
裝彈!
Reload! Reload!
發射裝置重新鎖定 鎖定炮閂
Reset! Secure the hatchet!
左舷準備完畢 拋掉錨!
Port side ready! Release the anchor!
炮彈來了!
Incoming! Incoming!
你沒事吧?
Are you alright?
別想打沉這艘船 沒門兒
They ain't gonna sink this battleship.No way.
開火!
Fire!
全部火力!
Everything you got!
所有飛機全部起飛 快
I want every available plane on this ship in the air! Now!
居然成功了
I can't believed that worked!
這是《孫子兵法》裡說的聲東擊西
Yea,Fight the enemy where they aren't
看了這麼多年 我終於懂了
After all these years,it finally just clicked
聲東擊西不是這個意思
That's not what it means
是嗎?
Really?
邊兒都不沾!
Not even close!
繼續開
Come on!
見鬼!
Shit!
我的腿卡住了
My leg's stuck.
米克!
Mick!
報告武器情況
Status,weapons.
三號炮塔沒了!
Turret 3 is down!
不過還剩下一顆高爆彈可以用
We got one round of high explosive back at turret 3
好 快叫大家去準備
Tell them to have it ready when you get there.
我來對付他
I got this.
比斯特 聽我說
Beast,update
我們需要這顆炮彈
I need that round
把它搬到二號炮塔去 - 長官?
You need to bring it to turret 2.- Sir?
二號炮塔離這兒五百英尺!
Turret 2 is 500 feet away!
這玩意兒有一千多磅重!
This round weighs over 1000 pounds!
我們怎麼把它弄過去?
How do we get it to there?
加油 把它搬到貨艙
move it into cargo hold
小心
be careful
雷克斯 你去炮塔 準備開火 - 是
Raikes,get to the gun plot inger on the trigger!- Yes sir.
加油 小心 小心點
Easy! Easy!
你快走!
Get outta here!
我們快走
We gotta go.
冷靜點 我是來救你的
Calm down! Ok?I'm gonna friggin save us!
炮塔準備就緒
Armed Turret 1!
坐標 T330
Coordinates 3-3-0!
高度 220
Elevation! 2-2-0.
弄開了
There! Go!
我們快走!
Let's go!
裝彈完畢
He's armed!
但願你已經下山了
You better not be up there
我們走 快點兒
Let's go! Come on!
霍伯!
Hopper!
我們就剩一顆炮彈了 是嗎?
We only have one round left,right?
對
Yea
很榮幸能和你並肩作戰
It's been an honor serving with you captain
我也很榮幸
The honor was mine
開火
Fire
開火!
Fire!
鎖定目標!
Locked on target!
為那些在面對來勢洶洶的敵人時
We take great pride in honoring
表現出非凡勇氣的女士們和先生們
the many men and women who demonstrated exceptional gallantry
感到自豪和驕傲
in the face of over-whelming enemy force
有太多的人在戰鬥中表現英勇
Valor and courage were exhibited by so many
我無法一一列舉
and I cannot honor them all
不過我很榮幸能在這裡
It is my great privilege to recognize those few whose actions
對其中的一些人給予特別表揚
deserve special acknowledgment
已經退役的美國陸軍中校
Lt-Col,United States Army retired
米克·卡納萊斯
Mick Canales
美利堅合眾國總統將這枚
President of the United States takes great pleasure in presenting
海軍十字勛章授予斯通·霍伯中校
the Navy Cross to Commander Stone Hopper.
以表彰他的英雄壯舉
For extraordinary heroism.
代替他的哥哥接受嘉獎是
Receiving this award,on behalf of his brother
亞歷克斯·霍伯少校
Lt Commander Alex Hopper
請留步 霍伯少校
Stand fast,Mr.Hopper
我很榮幸地授予你銀星勛章
It is my great pleasure,to present you with the Silver star,
以此表彰你的勇敢
for your exceptional heroism
以及傑出的作戰指揮
and gallantry in combat operations
我很期待不久以後
And I look forward to seeing you
看到你指揮自己的戰艦
at sea on a ship of your own command soon
謝謝
Thank you
夥計們 我會很想你們的
Guys I will miss you
奧蒂 先別說話
Orly  stop talking
過來拍張照 比斯特
Come on,take the picture,Beast
說"海軍"!
Say "Navy"!
海軍!
Navy!
表現不錯 霍伯
I'm impressed,Hopper!
準備好告別那些驅逐艦
You ready to get your ass on that big grey monster get out to Coronato
到基地來和大人物一起工作了嗎?
Get your hands dirty with the big boys?
是的 - 你有這個水平嗎?
Yes sir - You think you got what it takes?
應該有吧
I hope so sir.
給我打電話 霍伯!
Call me,Hopper!
不過在基地太無聊了
It just might be too much sleep though sir
你覺得在基地很無聊嗎? - 是的
Too much sleep for you huh? - Yes sir.
我們走著瞧
We'll have to see about that!
來吧 霍伯 和永田靠近點
Come on,Hopper! Cosy up to Nagata
你太可愛了 你們倆挺班配啊
You look so cute.You guys make a great couple
你想撮合我們啊?
Are we dating now?
大家說"海軍"!
Say "Navy"!
我可不說
No i don't know!
對不起 就小一會兒
Sorry! just for a moment
祝賀你 - 謝謝
Congratulations - Thank you.
你好嗎? - 挺好的 我愛你
How are you? - Good.I love you
我真的很幸運
I'm a luck guy,you know that?
我覺得現在最適合你去跟我爸談
would be the perfect time for you to talk to my dad
他在哪兒? 我希望他就在邊上
Where is he?I wish he was right here
太好了 快看
Oh it's perfect coz look!
你的願望成真了 快去吧!
My wish came true honey.Go get em!
好吧 我豁出去了
Thumbs up.That helps.
長官!
Sir!
什麼事?
What is it?
我想告訴你我真的很愛薩姆
I want you to know that I'm in love Sam
我希望您能允許我娶您的女兒
I am asking your permission to marry your daughter
不行!
No!
謝謝 長官 這真是...
Thank you sir! I mean it's..
什麼?
What?
不行
No
長官
Sir..
我拯救了全世界
I saved the world?
拯救世界又怎麼樣?霍伯
Saving the world is one thing,Hopper!
和我女兒不是一回事
My daughter is quite another
可是
Ye,but.
不行就是不行 霍伯
No means no,Hopper!
我得走了 我還沒吃飯呢
Now if you'll excuse me,I'm late for lunch
我打算去吃個雞肉卷
Think I'll have a Chicken Burrito
雞肉卷?
A Chicken Burrito?
長官!
Sir!
一起來吧 霍伯!
Come along,Hopper!
我們順便談談你的投降條件
We'll discuss the terms of your surrender over a meal
是 長官
Yes sir.
她跟你說了?
She told you about that?
別走開 7分鐘後 還有劇情！
觀看最新高清大片 請登陸www.66ys.net
獨家字幕製作：~Me愛FFS/WTF
字幕提供者QQ：28859861
蘇格蘭 北部高地
你根本超不過傑斯
連我都追不到碧昂斯
我也追不到她 想也別想
那是什麼
別靠太近
夥計們 快看那個
別太靠近
先別過去
這像不像一扇門 門嗎
喂 有人嗎
你這樣敲沒用的
沒用的
你知道這是什麼嗎
我們覺得裡面有東西
你能打開它嗎
只要我說能打開就能打開
加油 吉米
搞定了 來爸爸這兒
加油 吉米 使勁兒啊
就快打開了